<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Services on MM Custom Contracting Ltd Construction Services</title><link>http://latitude85-mmcustomltd.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/services/</link><description>Recent content in Services on MM Custom Contracting Ltd Construction Services</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="http://latitude85-mmcustomltd.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Basement &amp; Legal Suite Development</title><link>http://latitude85-mmcustomltd.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/services/basement-legal-suite-development/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://latitude85-mmcustomltd.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/services/basement-legal-suite-development/</guid><description>Looking to leverage your basement to make rental revenue? MM Custom can help you convert your basement into a self-contained legal basement suite. MM Custom can guide you through the in&amp;rsquo;s and out&amp;rsquo;s of this type of conversion with the guarantee that meets all regulations and is up to code. For more information or to find out if you are legible for this kind of conversion don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to call us.</description></item><item><title>Demolition &amp; Waste Management</title><link>http://latitude85-mmcustomltd.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/services/demolition-waste-management/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://latitude85-mmcustomltd.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/services/demolition-waste-management/</guid><description>MM Custom provides complete demolition and waste management services to a wide range of industrial, residential, and commercial clients. Whether it’s a small-scale project or a larger more complex project requiring extensive pre-project process planning, we deliver superior service and results. You can rest assured that waste management complies with all federal and provincial regulations and is dealt with in a sustainable way.</description></item><item><title>Design</title><link>http://latitude85-mmcustomltd.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/services/interior-renovation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://latitude85-mmcustomltd.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/services/interior-renovation/</guid><description>MM Custom is passionate about design</description></item><item><title>Exterior Renovation</title><link>http://latitude85-mmcustomltd.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/services/exterior-renovation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://latitude85-mmcustomltd.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/services/exterior-renovation/</guid><description>MM Custom has over 10 years of industry experience with exterior renovations. From small to large transformations we work with you and your budget to make sure you get durable results.</description></item><item><title>Interior Renovation</title><link>http://latitude85-mmcustomltd.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/services/interior-renovation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://latitude85-mmcustomltd.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/services/interior-renovation/</guid><description>MM Custom is passionate about the art of home customization. If its time for a kitchen renovation or your basement is overdue for an update, you can count on us to get the job done. Our passion for design is unbeatable, and we cant wait to transform your living space.</description></item><item><title>Safety Management &amp; Certification</title><link>http://latitude85-mmcustomltd.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/services/safety-management/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://latitude85-mmcustomltd.s3-website-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/services/safety-management/</guid><description>At MM Custom we put ourselves in your shoes, we adapt our services to meet your company’s unique needs. We can help you set up the safety program that fits your industry and way of working. The Alberta Certificate of Recognition (COR) is awarded to employers who develop efficient health and safety management systems which meet the provincial standards. These certificates are issued by Alberta Labour and are co-signed by the Certifying Partner in partnership with the Alberta government.</description></item></channel></rss>